Good morning, Miss Claire!
Ready to start the day?
Huh?
Yes, exactly.
Sister, you're too much!
Ray, I didn't hear you come in.
Oh, my apologies, and good morning.
You've turned up dreadfully late today.
Fortunately for you,
Sister took care of my preparations,
and she was absolutely amazing at it.
Well, I have a lot of practice from
taking care of you when we were younger.
That is so sweet.
But seeing Tim as Claire's
daily needs is my obsession.
Occupation.
And I wouldn't feel right
making you do my work for me.
You were about to say something
unnerving and cough to cover it up.
It really isn't a bother.
I'm actually enjoying every minute of it.
You know, Claire, you should
let me help you out every day.
How would you like to
have me as your maid?
Sister, you have to stop
teasing me like that.
I do apologize, love.
You're just so adorable when you blush.
Now, come with me, my princess.
Allow me to escort you to the dining hall.
Do you want me no hold on?
I'm not a thing.
Oh, I want only you!
Do you want me no hold on?
I want only you Do
you want me no hold on?
You know that the world is
not easy I can't believe you,
I can't believe you I can't believe you,
I can't believe you If
you want to see you,
So let's make a difference
no I I'm the only one
choice I'm the only one
choice From the heart of the
heart Raise your hands, give it up
Raise your hands,
take your hands
Don't you forget to leave it alone?
I love you
Are you all right, Ray?
You look a little ill.
I'm suffering from Miss Claire withdrawal.
Okay, it sounds like
everything's normal then.
Sleep well.
Why do you not leave
me in my time of need?
Princess Manaria is a menace.
I'm not even getting quality
properly and she's feeding Ms.
Claire with a spoon?
Uh, not cool!
It should've been me!
I was wrong.
This is beyond illness.
What happened?
Did you do something
to offend the princess?
Hmm.
You know, this might be a good
chance for you to get over Ms.
Claire.
Never will I!
My existence is dedicated to her!
If she's not in my world, then I
might as well drop dead! No, Ms.
Claire!
Means no life.
Well, I suppose you'll
have to fight for her then.
Hmm.
If I did,
I'm pretty sure I'd be playing right
into princess minaria's hands what do you
mean by that it feels like she's trying
to provoke me then your only choice is
to put up with it at least that way you
can still spend some time with miss claire
right in the game princess Manaria shows
up and becomes an ally to the heroine
so why would she be taking miss
claire's side it doesn't make any sense
i guess in the end it doesn't matter as
long as miss claire is happy i'm fine
she was so down after losing lenae but now
she's finally started smiling again and
i know it's because of her so i'm grateful
to princess Manaria at least i think so
What's the matter, Peppy?
As expected,
a big monster extermination is being
planned for this year's Amor ceremony.
For the ceremony?
Why?
Monsters will be drawn to the forest by
the magic stone and the scales of love.
They're not very strong,
but they arrive in greater numbers
than the military can handle alone.
It's gonna take everyone in this
academy to help take them down.
To ensure everyone's safety on the day,
we'll need to act in groups of three.
I advise you to coordinate your teams now.
May I have the honor of
being on a team with you?
Of course.
Nothing would please me more
than to have you by my side.
That's where I'm gonna be too!
The ceremony's so close, you can
almost feel the excitement in the air.
By the way, how is the winner determined
when the suitors make their offerings?
Surely it can't be as simple as
whichever one is heavier, right?
Oh no!
Physical weight has nothing
to do with the outcome.
It's not the offerings the scales weigh,
but the strength of the suitor's feelings.
Actually,
in the game,
the winner was determined by how
difficult their offering was to obtain.
The weightiest offerings
are the flowers of flora.
With those on the scales,
a suitor is certain to win.
You're talking about the flowers of
light mentioned in Poesia Moor, right?
They really exist?
Well, yes, but they're incredibly
rare and grow in hard-to-reach places.
The ceremony really follows the
legend down to the last detail, huh?
That's amazing.
Personally, I don't think Poesia
Moor is a very good story.
I've never really liked it.
Oh, what makes you say that? I mean,
why couldn't the priestess just choose
which one of the men she wanted to be with?
It's almost like she wanted
them to fight over her.
Pretty villainous of her if you ask me.
That's an unfair assessment.
See, I think she simply couldn't decide.
When you truly fall in love, it
must be an overwhelming experience,
making it difficult for even you
yourself to discern how you really feel.
Well, maybe that's how
it works for some people.
You know what they say, love is blind.
Yeah, but I don't think
that's quite what they meant.
Ray, would you mind
pouring me some more tea?
I'm sorry, it's empty, but
I'll go make another pot.
Yes, please do.
Oh, and there's no need to rush.
On the contrary, I very
much think there is.
Well, we should go now.
I'm sure that we'll see
you around sometime.
Well, that was rather strange.
What?
Peppy and Loretta?
No, I meant the commoner.
Her behavior has been questionable lately.
Oh, you observe Ray
pretty closely, don't you?
Of course I do.
I wouldn't be a very
responsible master if I didn't.
Hmm.
And yet you don't know
what's wrong with her.
Right.
What was it you said before?
About love being blind?
Sorry, what was that? Hmm?
Oh, it's nothing, really.
We need to have a word with you!
Oh, hey there, Minibus Squadron.
Sorry I can't remember your real name.
Not only are you the most insulent
commoner ever, you're also quite stupid!
I apologize, there's only enough room
in my brain for Miss Claire's wishes.
So, uh, what do you want from me?
Frankly, I can't comprehend half
of the things you say or do.
But, um...
We wanted to ask if you're being honest
about your feelings for Miss Claire.
Are you?
Look, no matter what happens, you must
promise you'll protect Miss Claire.
You're her personal maid, so can you
guard her from morning until night?
Even if you have to go up against royalty?
What royalty?
Hold on, are you talking
about Princess Manaria?
Hush, don't speak so loudly.
Okie dokie, then.
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
We heard that Princess Manaria has, um,
let's say, a track record among the
ladies of the night in her kingdom.
Rumor's right.
People spread the strangest things.
But regardless, if anything
happens to Miss Claire,
know that we'll be looking for you.
Loretta, I can't help but wonder if we
asked the wrong person to help us with this.
Please don't say that.
I simply can't process it right now.
Well, good night, Miss Clare.
See you in the morning.
I admire your patience, Ray.
Do you have a moment to talk?
You're in love with
Miss Clare, aren't you?
Yet you've been awfully well-behaved
lately, even after all my provocations.
So it's true.
You were trying to provoke me.
I do love Miss Clare, you're right.
That said, I've never expected
her to return my feelings.
The only thing that matters
to me is her happiness.
Is that so?
I didn't realize your feelings
for her were so shallow.
I'm unfortunate.
I beg your pardon?
What do you mean my feelings
for her are shallow?
Figure of speech.
Did I hit a nerve?
My apologies.
With all due respect,
the way I feel for Miss Claire is
something you could never comprehend.
And yet you're giving up on her.
I am not giving up on her.
I already told you I'm
putting her happiness first.
No, you're being a coward.
If you had a spine, you would fight to make
her happier than anyone else ever could.
That's not...
I'd do anything to make Miss Claire
happy for as long as she'd let me.
But I'm a commoner, and we're both girls.
That's not what she wants in a partner.
So I'd never make her as
happy as she deserves to be.
You shouldn't run.
I'm not running.
Really?
Then try to take her back from me.
It sounds like you're
trying to pick a fight.
I am.
Did you just figure that out?
You're just as weak as your love for Claire
is, and I'm going to make you face it.
You'll thank me.
I'm doing you both a kindness.
All right, Princess.
If you want to fight, you've got one!
Good.
That's what I hoped you'd say.
Well then, meet me after school
tomorrow at the Magic Practice Ground.
And don't run away.
My love isn't weak, and
I'll prove it to you!
She's going up against
Ray Taylor this time?
This ought to be good.
Who do you think will win?
Sister, I don't understand.
What made you decide to
go through with this?
It's just a friendly test of skill.
I'm ready to go when you are, Ray.
Took you long enough.
You've got spirit.
That's good to know.
Well, let's begin.
Are you both ready? Ready.
All right.
On your marks, go!
Let's see what you can do.
And straight to the pitfall trap that
won her the match against Claire.
It's a somewhat effective strategy, but...
Not a bad opener.
But you still don't have what
it takes to win against me.
You sure?
You might want to look up.
Water Meteor!
Sister, no!
A fusion of earth and water magic.
That's some pretty insane power she has.
Even Manaria is having trouble.
I'm not so sure.
How rude.
You got my clothes all wet.
An exceptional level wind spell.
Teleport.
The way that played out, I'd say she must
have had some idea of what was coming.
But it's still tough to deflect.
I'm insulted.
This better not mean that she was
holding back against me during our duel.
You're going all in right
from the start, huh?
Well, I don't exactly have much of a choice
when I'm up against someone like you.
Princess Manaria can use Spellbreaker.
If the battle drags out, she'll
analyze all my spells and erase them.
I'm not taking that chance.
What's the matter?
You're not about to call
it quits now, are you?
Yeah, right!
In your dreams!
This move is a high-level
spell that players
normally can't use until
the end of the game.
Chain spell.
Code, hide it!
It's the highest level of
attack I have right now.
This should do it.
Well done.
That was very close.
If it was anyone else you were up against,
you probably would have
just won the match.
How did you manage to dodge all that?
I'm not telling.
Teleport, maybe?
No, there wasn't quite enough time.
Reaction speeds off the
charts like everything else.
Tell me something, Ray.
Don't you think that was a bit too much?
Even if we are under a
magic dampening barrier,
if that had hit me directly, I would
have been more than just a bit injured.
And yet you evaded it
without breaking a sweat.
Well, consider who you're battling.
Since you managed to give me such an
entertaining show, maybe I'll return the favor.
Oh no, I know what's coming.
I'll have to use Kokaitis again.
No, that won't work.
What do I do?
I have nothing to counter with.
You're finished!
Dominator.
Dominator, a spell that
uses all four attributes.
It takes control of the victim's
magic and makes it go berserk.
It's the most brutal
attack spell there is.
And against another spellcaster,
the ultimate weapon.
Commoner!
Are you all right?
No! Wake up!
Commoner! Commoner!
Open your eyes now!
Commoner!
Wake up!
Step aside, Claire. I'll heal her.
Please, sister.
She's going to be all right.
There's no need to worry.
It wasn't necessary to go that far!
Your standard magic and spellbreaker would
have been more than
enough to win the duel,
but you just had to keep pushing!
What if the worst had happened?
You could have killed her!
There was always a barrier.
Even Dominator couldn't have
inflicted lethal damage.
Although, I have to admit it was
more powerful than I thought.
Ray must have quite a bit of
magic if it hurt her that much.
How can you be so calm?
You worry about her a
lot, don't you, Claire?
Miss Claire.
Thank goodness.
Did I win?
Unfortunately, you lost.
That's right.
I remember now.
I knew that Princess Manaria had
the ability to use Dominator.
I know everything about
the world of this game.
And because of that...
A deal is a deal.
You've been defeated,
and now Claire is mine.
I know.
I can never beat her.
Thank you.
Come back.
I was talking to you.
Just leave her be for now.
She's fine. Foolish girl.
We were instructed to
form teams for a reason.
It's dangerous.
Ray will be perfectly safe on her own.
Nothing's going to happen.
I promise.
You left my side without
so much as a word.
Miss Claire.
A servant should never abandon her master.
Besides.
Wandering off by yourself when you haven't
gotten your full strength back yet.
It's rash and irresponsible.
I don't see the problem.
You have Princess Manaria, don't you?
The world's one and only quadcaster.
With her to protect you, you
should be perfectly safe.
My safety isn't what I'm talking about!
Something has been bothering you, and ever
since the duel, it's only gotten worse.
I'm fine. Nothing's wrong.
Don't lie to me!
The way you're acting, even
Raylaire won't go near you.
You're quiet.
So quiet, it's frightening.
You want to know the truth?
We fought that duel with you
as the stakes, Miss Claire.
I lost it.
And you too.
I don't have the right to
stay by your side anymore.
Of all the ridiculous,
you were fighting over me?
I am not something to be one!
How dare you two!
Come on, be honest.
It makes you feel good, doesn't it?
Being wanted by someone as
amazing as Princess Manaria?
She was your first love,
right? Your prince.
I am your master.
You're my maid.
Kindly act like it!
You're sulking like a child, running from
everything because you lost one match?
Unbelievable.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
I'm ashamed of you.
In fact,
if you continue to behave like this, then
you will no longer be fit to serve me.
That works out well, because I quit.
What did you just say?
I'm quitting my job as your maid.
Don't tell me you actually mean that.
I see.
Very well, then.
I may have had a few complaints,
but you have served me competently.
On behalf of the Francois
family, I offer my gratitude.
Please accept, Miss Taylor.
Ms. Clare!
There's nothing keeping you now.
I apologize for all of the
selfish demands I've made of you.
Whatever your future holds,
I pray you find happiness.
I've made a mistake, haven't I?
I'll be going then.
A fatal mistake.
One that I can't take back.
I'm not surprised.
You're leaving just like
everyone else in my life.
You liar.
You